<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="com.cubrid.cubridmigration.plugin.feature"
      label="CUBRID Migration Toolkit Plug-in"
      version="9.3.0.qualifier"
      provider-name="CUBRID"
      plugin="com.cubrid.cubridmigration.plugin">

   <description url="http://www.cubrid.org">
      CUBRID Migration Toolkit
   </description>

   <copyright url="http://www.cubrid.org">
      Copyright (C) Search Solution Corporation. All rights reserved.
CUBRID is a registered trademark of Search Solution Corporation and 
CUBRID Migration Toolkit is a name of program for migrating schema and data to CUBRID. 

CUBRID Migration Toolkit is released under BSD license. 
For more information, please refer to the CUBRID home page(http://www.cubrid.org).

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:
 - Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
 - Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.
 - Neither the name of Search Solution Coporation nor the names of its contributors may be used to endorse or promote products derived from this software without specific prior written permission.

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS &quot;AS IS&quot; AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT OWNER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Oracle and MySQL JDBC drivers included in the CUBRID Migration Toolkit program are 
released under Oracle Technology Network Development and Distribution License Agreement and 
You shall no right to distribute JDBC drivers in the program by the Agreement
(http://www.oracle.com/technetwork/licenses/distribution-license-152002.html).

License Rights 
We grant you a nonexclusive, nontransferable limited license to use the programs: (a) for purposes of developing, testing, prototyping and running applications you have developed for your own internal data processing operations; (b) to distribute the programs with applications you have developed to your customers provided that each such licensee agrees to license terms consistent with the terms of this Agreement, you do not charge your end users any additional fees for the use of the programs, and your end users may only use the programs to run your applications for their own business operations; and (c) to use the programs to provide third party demonstrations and training. You are not permitted to use the programs for any purpose other than as permitted under this Agreement. If you want to use the programs for any purpose other than as expressly permitted under this agreement you must contact us, or an Oracle reseller, to obtain the appropriate license. We may audit your use and distribution of the programs. Program documentation is either shipped with the programs, or documentation may accessed online at http://otn.oracle.com/docs.

Ownership and Restrictions 
We retain all ownership and intellectual property rights in the programs. You may make a sufficient number of copies of the programs for the licensed use and one copy of the programs for backup purposes.

You may not: 
- use the programs for any purpose other than as provided above; 
- distribute the programs unless accompanied with your applications; 
- charge your end users for use of the programs; 
- remove or modify any program markings or any notice of our proprietary rights; 
- use the programs to provide third party training on the content and/or functionality of the programs, except for training your licensed users; 
- assign this agreement or give the programs, program access or an interest in the programs to any individual or entity except as provided under this agreement; 
- cause or permit reverse engineering (unless required by law for interoperability), disassembly or decompilation of the programs; 
- disclose results of any program benchmark tests without our prior consent.

Program Distribution 
We grant you a nonexclusive, nontransferable right to copy and distribute the programs to your end users provided that you do not charge your end users for use of the programs and provided your end users may only use the programs to run your applications for their business operations. Prior to distributing the programs you shall require your end users to execute an agreement binding them to terms consistent with those contained in this section and the sections of this agreement entitled &quot;License Rights,&quot; &quot;Ownership and Restrictions,&quot; &quot;Export,&quot; &quot;Disclaimer of Warranties and Exclusive Remedies,&quot; &quot;No Technical Support,&quot; &quot;End of Agreement,&quot; &quot;Relationship Between the Parties,&quot; and &quot;Open Source.&quot; You must also include a provision stating that your end users shall have no right to distribute the programs, and a provision specifying us as a third party beneficiary of the agreement. You are responsible for obtaining these agreements with your end users.

You agree to: (a) defend and indemnify us against all claims and damages caused by your distribution of the programs in breach of this agreements and/or failure to include the required contractual provisions in your end user agreement as stated above; (b) keep executed end user agreements and records of end user information including name, address, date of distribution and identity of programs distributed; (c) allow us to inspect your end user agreements and records upon request; and, (d) enforce the terms of your end user agreements so as to effect a timely cure of any end user breach, and to notify us of any breach of the terms.

Export 
You agree that U.S. export control laws and other applicable export and import laws govern your use of the programs, including technical data; additional information can be found on Oracle&apos;s Global Trade Compliance web site located at http://www.oracle.com/products/export/index.html?content.html. You agree that neither the programs nor any direct product thereof will be exported, directly, or indirectly, in violation of these laws, or will be used for any purpose prohibited by these laws including, without limitation, nuclear, chemical, or biological weapons proliferation.

Disclaimer of Warranty and Exclusive Remedies

THE PROGRAMS ARE PROVIDED &quot;AS IS&quot; WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND. WE FURTHER DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS AND IMPLIED, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR NONINFRINGEMENT.

IN NO EVENT SHALL WE BE LIABLE FOR ANY INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, OR DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS, REVENUE, DATA OR DATA USE, INCURRED BY YOU OR ANY THIRD PARTY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION IN CONTRACT OR TORT, EVEN IF WE HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. OUR ENTIRE LIABILITY FOR DAMAGES HEREUNDER SHALL IN NO EVENT EXCEED ONE THOUSAND DOLLARS (U.S. $1,000).

No Technical Support 
Our technical support organization will not provide technical support, phone support, or updates to you for the programs licensed under this agreement.

Restricted Rights 
If you distribute a license to the United States government, the programs, including documentation, shall be considered commercial computer software and you will place a legend, in addition to applicable copyright notices, on the documentation, and on the media label, substantially similar to the following: 

NOTICE OF RESTRICTED RIGHTS 

&quot;Programs delivered subject to the DOD FAR Supplement are &apos;commercial computer software&apos; and use, duplication, and disclosure of the programs, including documentation, shall be subject to the licensing restrictions set forth in the applicable Oracle license agreement. Otherwise, programs delivered subject to the Federal Acquisition Regulations are &apos;restricted computer software&apos; and use, duplication, and disclosure of the programs, including documentation, shall be subject to the restrictions in FAR 52.227-19, Commercial Computer Software-Restricted Rights (June 1987). Oracle America, Inc., 500 Oracle Parkway, Redwood City, CA 94065.&quot;

End of Agreement 
You may terminate this agreement by destroying all copies of the programs. We have the right to terminate your right to use the programs if you fail to comply with any of the terms of this agreement, in which case you shall destroy all copies of the programs.

Relationship Between the Parties 
The relationship between you and us is that of licensee/licensor. Neither party will represent that it has any authority to assume or create any obligation, express or implied, on behalf of the other party, nor to represent the other party as agent, employee, franchisee, or in any other capacity. Nothing in this agreement shall be construed to limit either party&apos;s right to independently develop or distribute software that is functionally similar to the other party&apos;s products, so long as proprietary information of the other party is not included in such software.

Open Source 
&quot;Open Source&quot; software - software available without charge for use, modification and distribution - is often licensed under terms that require the user to make the user&apos;s modifications to the Open Source software or any software that the user &apos;combines&apos; with the Open Source software freely available in source code form. If you use Open Source software in conjunction with the programs, you must ensure that your use does not: (i) create, or purport to create, obligations of us with respect to the Oracle programs; or (ii) grant, or purport to grant, to any third party any rights to or immunities under our intellectual property or proprietary rights in the Oracle programs. For example, you may not develop a software program using an Oracle program and an Open Source program where such use results in a program file(s) that contains code from both the Oracle program and the Open Source program (including without limitation libraries) if the Open Source program is licensed under a license that requires any &quot;modifications&quot; be made freely available. You also may not combine the Oracle program with programs licensed under the GNU General Public License (&quot;GPL&quot;) in any manner that could cause, or could be interpreted or asserted to cause, the Oracle program or any modifications thereto to become subject to the terms of the GPL.

Entire Agreement 
You agree that this agreement is the complete agreement for the programs and licenses, and this agreement supersedes all prior or contemporaneous agreements or representations. If any term of this agreement is found to be invalid or unenforceable, the remaining provisions will remain effective.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------

MSSQL JDBC drivers included in the CUBRID Migration Toolkit program are 
released under MICROSOFT SOFTWARE LICENSE TERMS and MICROSOFT SQL SERVER JDBC DRIVER REDISTRIBUTION LICENSE.  
You shall no right to distribute JDBC drivers in the program by the Agreement
(http://msdn.microsoft.com/ko-kr/data/aa937726).

MICROSOFT SOFTWARE LICENSE TERMS
MICROSOFT SQL SERVER JDBC DRIVER REDISTRIBUTION LICENSE
These license terms are an agreement between Microsoft Corporation (or based on where you live, one of its affiliates) and you. Please read them. They apply to the software named above, which includes the media on which you received it, if any. The terms also apply to any Microsoft

updates,
supplements,
Internet-based services, and
support services
for this software, unless other terms accompany those items. If so, those terms apply.

By using the software, you accept these terms. If you do not accept them, do not use the software. If you comply with these license terms, you have the rights below.

1.INSTALLATION AND USE RIGHTS. You may use any number of copies of the software on your devices.

2.ADDITIONAL LICENSING REQUIREMENTS AND/OR USE RIGHTS.
a.Distributable Code. You are permitted to distribute the software in programs you develop if you comply with the terms below.
i.Right to Use and Distribute. The software is &quot;Distributable Code.&quot;
-Distributable Code. You may copy and distribute the object code form of the software. You may not modify the software.
-Third Party Distribution. You may permit distributors of your programs to copy and distribute the Distributable Code as part of those programs.
ii.Distribution Requirements. For any Distributable Code you distribute, you must
-add significant primary functionality to it in your programs;
-require distributors and external end users to agree to terms that protect it at least as much as this agreement; 
-display your valid copyright notice on your programs; and
-indemnify, defend, and hold harmless Microsoft from any claims, including attorneys&apos; fees, related to the distribution or use of your programs.
iii.Distribution Restrictions. You may not
-alter any copyright, trademark or patent notice in the Distributable Code;
-use Microsoft&apos;s trademarks in your programs&apos; names or in a way that suggests your programs come from or are endorsed by Microsoft; 
-include Distributable Code in malicious, deceptive or unlawful programs; or
-modify or distribute the source code of any Distributable Code so that any part of it becomes subject to an Excluded License. An Excluded License is one that requires, as a condition of use, modification or distribution, that
-the code be disclosed or distributed in source code form; or 
-others have the right to modify it.

3.SCOPE OF LICENSE. The software is licensed, not sold. This agreement only gives you some rights to use the software. Microsoft reserves all other rights. Unless applicable law gives you more rights despite this limitation, you may use the software only as expressly permitted in this agreement. In doing so, you must comply with any technical limitations in the software that only allow you to use it in certain ways. You may not
-disclose the results of any benchmark tests of the software to any third party without Microsoft&apos;s prior written approval;
-reverse engineer, decompile or disassemble the software, except and only to the extent that applicable law expressly permits, despite this limitation;
-publish the software for others to copy; or
-rent, lease or lend the software.

4.TRANSFER TO A THIRD PARTY. The first user of the software may transfer it and this agreement directly to a third party. Before the transfer, that party must agree that this agreement applies to the transfer and use of the software. The first user must uninstall the software before transferring it separately from the device. The first user may not retain any copies.
5.EXPORT RESTRICTIONS. The software is subject to United States export laws and regulations. You must comply with all domestic and international export laws and regulations that apply to the software. These laws include restrictions on destinations, end users and end use. For additional information, see www.microsoft.com/exporting.
6.SUPPORT SERVICES. Because this software is &quot;as is,&quot; we may not provide support services for it.
7.ENTIRE AGREEMENT. This agreement, and the terms for supplements, updates, Internet-based services and support services that you use, are the entire agreement for the software and support services.
8.APPLICABLE LAW.
a.United States. If you acquired the software in the United States, Washington state law governs the interpretation of this agreement and applies to claims for breach of it, regardless of conflict of laws principles. The laws of the state where you live govern all other claims, including claims under state consumer protection laws, unfair competition laws, and in tort.
b.Outside the United States. If you acquired the software in any other country, the laws of that country apply.
9.LEGAL EFFECT. This agreement describes certain legal rights. You may have other rights under the laws of your country. You may also have rights with respect to the party from whom you acquired the software. This agreement does not change your rights under the laws of your country if the laws of your country do not permit it to do so.
10.DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTY. The software is licensed &quot;as-is.&quot; You bear the risk of using it. Microsoft gives no express warranties, guarantees or conditions. You may have additional consumer rights under your local laws which this agreement cannot change. To the extent permitted under your local laws, Microsoft excludes the implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose and non-infringement.
11.LIMITATION ON AND EXCLUSION OF REMEDIES AND DAMAGES. You can recover from Microsoft and its suppliers only direct damages up to U.S. $5.00. You cannot recover any other damages, including consequential, lost profits, special, indirect or incidental damages.
This limitation applies to

-anything related to the software, services, content (including code) on third party Internet sites, or third party programs; and
-claims for breach of contract, breach of warranty, guarantee or condition, strict liability, negligence, or other tort to the extent permitted by applicable law.
It also applies even if Microsoft knew or should have known about the possibility of the damages. The above limitation or exclusion may not apply to you because your country may not allow the exclusion or limitation of incidental, consequential or other damages.
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

If You have any questions concerning this License Agreement, 
please ask any on CUBRID Forum at http://forum.cubrid.org.

Sincerely,
Your CUBRID Tool Development Team.
   </copyright>

   <license url="http://www.cubrid.org">
      Copyright (C) Search Solution Corporation. All rights reserved.
CUBRID is a registered trademark of Search Solution Corporation and 
CUBRID Migration Toolkit is a name of program for migrating schema and data to CUBRID. 

CUBRID Migration Toolkit is released under BSD license. 
For more information, please refer to the CUBRID home page(http://www.cubrid.org).

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:
 - Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
 - Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.
 - Neither the name of Search Solution Coporation nor the names of its contributors may be used to endorse or promote products derived from this software without specific prior written permission.

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS &quot;AS IS&quot; AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT OWNER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Oracle and MySQL JDBC drivers included in the CUBRID Migration Toolkit program are 
released under Oracle Technology Network Development and Distribution License Agreement and 
You shall no right to distribute JDBC drivers in the program by the Agreement
(http://www.oracle.com/technetwork/licenses/distribution-license-152002.html).

License Rights 
We grant you a nonexclusive, nontransferable limited license to use the programs: (a) for purposes of developing, testing, prototyping and running applications you have developed for your own internal data processing operations; (b) to distribute the programs with applications you have developed to your customers provided that each such licensee agrees to license terms consistent with the terms of this Agreement, you do not charge your end users any additional fees for the use of the programs, and your end users may only use the programs to run your applications for their own business operations; and (c) to use the programs to provide third party demonstrations and training. You are not permitted to use the programs for any purpose other than as permitted under this Agreement. If you want to use the programs for any purpose other than as expressly permitted under this agreement you must contact us, or an Oracle reseller, to obtain the appropriate license. We may audit your use and distribution of the programs. Program documentation is either shipped with the programs, or documentation may accessed online at http://otn.oracle.com/docs.

Ownership and Restrictions 
We retain all ownership and intellectual property rights in the programs. You may make a sufficient number of copies of the programs for the licensed use and one copy of the programs for backup purposes.

You may not: 
- use the programs for any purpose other than as provided above; 
- distribute the programs unless accompanied with your applications; 
- charge your end users for use of the programs; 
- remove or modify any program markings or any notice of our proprietary rights; 
- use the programs to provide third party training on the content and/or functionality of the programs, except for training your licensed users; 
- assign this agreement or give the programs, program access or an interest in the programs to any individual or entity except as provided under this agreement; 
- cause or permit reverse engineering (unless required by law for interoperability), disassembly or decompilation of the programs; 
- disclose results of any program benchmark tests without our prior consent.

Program Distribution 
We grant you a nonexclusive, nontransferable right to copy and distribute the programs to your end users provided that you do not charge your end users for use of the programs and provided your end users may only use the programs to run your applications for their business operations. Prior to distributing the programs you shall require your end users to execute an agreement binding them to terms consistent with those contained in this section and the sections of this agreement entitled &quot;License Rights,&quot; &quot;Ownership and Restrictions,&quot; &quot;Export,&quot; &quot;Disclaimer of Warranties and Exclusive Remedies,&quot; &quot;No Technical Support,&quot; &quot;End of Agreement,&quot; &quot;Relationship Between the Parties,&quot; and &quot;Open Source.&quot; You must also include a provision stating that your end users shall have no right to distribute the programs, and a provision specifying us as a third party beneficiary of the agreement. You are responsible for obtaining these agreements with your end users.

You agree to: (a) defend and indemnify us against all claims and damages caused by your distribution of the programs in breach of this agreements and/or failure to include the required contractual provisions in your end user agreement as stated above; (b) keep executed end user agreements and records of end user information including name, address, date of distribution and identity of programs distributed; (c) allow us to inspect your end user agreements and records upon request; and, (d) enforce the terms of your end user agreements so as to effect a timely cure of any end user breach, and to notify us of any breach of the terms.

Export 
You agree that U.S. export control laws and other applicable export and import laws govern your use of the programs, including technical data; additional information can be found on Oracle&apos;s Global Trade Compliance web site located at http://www.oracle.com/products/export/index.html?content.html. You agree that neither the programs nor any direct product thereof will be exported, directly, or indirectly, in violation of these laws, or will be used for any purpose prohibited by these laws including, without limitation, nuclear, chemical, or biological weapons proliferation.

Disclaimer of Warranty and Exclusive Remedies

THE PROGRAMS ARE PROVIDED &quot;AS IS&quot; WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND. WE FURTHER DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS AND IMPLIED, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR NONINFRINGEMENT.

IN NO EVENT SHALL WE BE LIABLE FOR ANY INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, OR DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS, REVENUE, DATA OR DATA USE, INCURRED BY YOU OR ANY THIRD PARTY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION IN CONTRACT OR TORT, EVEN IF WE HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. OUR ENTIRE LIABILITY FOR DAMAGES HEREUNDER SHALL IN NO EVENT EXCEED ONE THOUSAND DOLLARS (U.S. $1,000).

No Technical Support 
Our technical support organization will not provide technical support, phone support, or updates to you for the programs licensed under this agreement.

Restricted Rights 
If you distribute a license to the United States government, the programs, including documentation, shall be considered commercial computer software and you will place a legend, in addition to applicable copyright notices, on the documentation, and on the media label, substantially similar to the following: 

NOTICE OF RESTRICTED RIGHTS 

&quot;Programs delivered subject to the DOD FAR Supplement are &apos;commercial computer software&apos; and use, duplication, and disclosure of the programs, including documentation, shall be subject to the licensing restrictions set forth in the applicable Oracle license agreement. Otherwise, programs delivered subject to the Federal Acquisition Regulations are &apos;restricted computer software&apos; and use, duplication, and disclosure of the programs, including documentation, shall be subject to the restrictions in FAR 52.227-19, Commercial Computer Software-Restricted Rights (June 1987). Oracle America, Inc., 500 Oracle Parkway, Redwood City, CA 94065.&quot;

End of Agreement 
You may terminate this agreement by destroying all copies of the programs. We have the right to terminate your right to use the programs if you fail to comply with any of the terms of this agreement, in which case you shall destroy all copies of the programs.

Relationship Between the Parties 
The relationship between you and us is that of licensee/licensor. Neither party will represent that it has any authority to assume or create any obligation, express or implied, on behalf of the other party, nor to represent the other party as agent, employee, franchisee, or in any other capacity. Nothing in this agreement shall be construed to limit either party&apos;s right to independently develop or distribute software that is functionally similar to the other party&apos;s products, so long as proprietary information of the other party is not included in such software.

Open Source 
&quot;Open Source&quot; software - software available without charge for use, modification and distribution - is often licensed under terms that require the user to make the user&apos;s modifications to the Open Source software or any software that the user &apos;combines&apos; with the Open Source software freely available in source code form. If you use Open Source software in conjunction with the programs, you must ensure that your use does not: (i) create, or purport to create, obligations of us with respect to the Oracle programs; or (ii) grant, or purport to grant, to any third party any rights to or immunities under our intellectual property or proprietary rights in the Oracle programs. For example, you may not develop a software program using an Oracle program and an Open Source program where such use results in a program file(s) that contains code from both the Oracle program and the Open Source program (including without limitation libraries) if the Open Source program is licensed under a license that requires any &quot;modifications&quot; be made freely available. You also may not combine the Oracle program with programs licensed under the GNU General Public License (&quot;GPL&quot;) in any manner that could cause, or could be interpreted or asserted to cause, the Oracle program or any modifications thereto to become subject to the terms of the GPL.

Entire Agreement 
You agree that this agreement is the complete agreement for the programs and licenses, and this agreement supersedes all prior or contemporaneous agreements or representations. If any term of this agreement is found to be invalid or unenforceable, the remaining provisions will remain effective.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------

MSSQL JDBC drivers included in the CUBRID Migration Toolkit program are 
released under MICROSOFT SOFTWARE LICENSE TERMS and MICROSOFT SQL SERVER JDBC DRIVER REDISTRIBUTION LICENSE.  
You shall no right to distribute JDBC drivers in the program by the Agreement
(http://msdn.microsoft.com/ko-kr/data/aa937726).

MICROSOFT SOFTWARE LICENSE TERMS
MICROSOFT SQL SERVER JDBC DRIVER REDISTRIBUTION LICENSE
These license terms are an agreement between Microsoft Corporation (or based on where you live, one of its affiliates) and you. Please read them. They apply to the software named above, which includes the media on which you received it, if any. The terms also apply to any Microsoft

updates,
supplements,
Internet-based services, and
support services
for this software, unless other terms accompany those items. If so, those terms apply.

By using the software, you accept these terms. If you do not accept them, do not use the software. If you comply with these license terms, you have the rights below.

1.INSTALLATION AND USE RIGHTS. You may use any number of copies of the software on your devices.

2.ADDITIONAL LICENSING REQUIREMENTS AND/OR USE RIGHTS.
a.Distributable Code. You are permitted to distribute the software in programs you develop if you comply with the terms below.
i.Right to Use and Distribute. The software is &quot;Distributable Code.&quot;
-Distributable Code. You may copy and distribute the object code form of the software. You may not modify the software.
-Third Party Distribution. You may permit distributors of your programs to copy and distribute the Distributable Code as part of those programs.
ii.Distribution Requirements. For any Distributable Code you distribute, you must
-add significant primary functionality to it in your programs;
-require distributors and external end users to agree to terms that protect it at least as much as this agreement; 
-display your valid copyright notice on your programs; and
-indemnify, defend, and hold harmless Microsoft from any claims, including attorneys&apos; fees, related to the distribution or use of your programs.
iii.Distribution Restrictions. You may not
-alter any copyright, trademark or patent notice in the Distributable Code;
-use Microsoft&apos;s trademarks in your programs&apos; names or in a way that suggests your programs come from or are endorsed by Microsoft; 
-include Distributable Code in malicious, deceptive or unlawful programs; or
-modify or distribute the source code of any Distributable Code so that any part of it becomes subject to an Excluded License. An Excluded License is one that requires, as a condition of use, modification or distribution, that
-the code be disclosed or distributed in source code form; or 
-others have the right to modify it.

3.SCOPE OF LICENSE. The software is licensed, not sold. This agreement only gives you some rights to use the software. Microsoft reserves all other rights. Unless applicable law gives you more rights despite this limitation, you may use the software only as expressly permitted in this agreement. In doing so, you must comply with any technical limitations in the software that only allow you to use it in certain ways. You may not
-disclose the results of any benchmark tests of the software to any third party without Microsoft&apos;s prior written approval;
-reverse engineer, decompile or disassemble the software, except and only to the extent that applicable law expressly permits, despite this limitation;
-publish the software for others to copy; or
-rent, lease or lend the software.

4.TRANSFER TO A THIRD PARTY. The first user of the software may transfer it and this agreement directly to a third party. Before the transfer, that party must agree that this agreement applies to the transfer and use of the software. The first user must uninstall the software before transferring it separately from the device. The first user may not retain any copies.
5.EXPORT RESTRICTIONS. The software is subject to United States export laws and regulations. You must comply with all domestic and international export laws and regulations that apply to the software. These laws include restrictions on destinations, end users and end use. For additional information, see www.microsoft.com/exporting.
6.SUPPORT SERVICES. Because this software is &quot;as is,&quot; we may not provide support services for it.
7.ENTIRE AGREEMENT. This agreement, and the terms for supplements, updates, Internet-based services and support services that you use, are the entire agreement for the software and support services.
8.APPLICABLE LAW.
a.United States. If you acquired the software in the United States, Washington state law governs the interpretation of this agreement and applies to claims for breach of it, regardless of conflict of laws principles. The laws of the state where you live govern all other claims, including claims under state consumer protection laws, unfair competition laws, and in tort.
b.Outside the United States. If you acquired the software in any other country, the laws of that country apply.
9.LEGAL EFFECT. This agreement describes certain legal rights. You may have other rights under the laws of your country. You may also have rights with respect to the party from whom you acquired the software. This agreement does not change your rights under the laws of your country if the laws of your country do not permit it to do so.
10.DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTY. The software is licensed &quot;as-is.&quot; You bear the risk of using it. Microsoft gives no express warranties, guarantees or conditions. You may have additional consumer rights under your local laws which this agreement cannot change. To the extent permitted under your local laws, Microsoft excludes the implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose and non-infringement.
11.LIMITATION ON AND EXCLUSION OF REMEDIES AND DAMAGES. You can recover from Microsoft and its suppliers only direct damages up to U.S. $5.00. You cannot recover any other damages, including consequential, lost profits, special, indirect or incidental damages.
This limitation applies to

-anything related to the software, services, content (including code) on third party Internet sites, or third party programs; and
-claims for breach of contract, breach of warranty, guarantee or condition, strict liability, negligence, or other tort to the extent permitted by applicable law.
It also applies even if Microsoft knew or should have known about the possibility of the damages. The above limitation or exclusion may not apply to you because your country may not allow the exclusion or limitation of incidental, consequential or other damages.
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

If You have any questions concerning this License Agreement, 
please ask any on CUBRID Forum at http://forum.cubrid.org.

Sincerely,
Your CUBRID Tool Development Team.
   </license>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.runtime"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.equinox.p2.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.forms"/>
      <import plugin="com.cubrid.common.configuration" version="9.2.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="com.cubrid.cubridmigration.core"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.cubrid.cubridmigration.plugin"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.cubrid.cubridmigration.ui"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
